<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>BLOG_NAME</title>
 <link href="YOUR_URL/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="YOUR_URL"/>
 <updated>2015-06-08T21:20:17+00:00</updated>
 <id>BLOG_URL</id>
 <author>
   <name>BLOG_NAME</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>welcome_to_the_philosophical_poet</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/welcome-to-the-philosophical-poet.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/welcome-to-the-philosophical-poet</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;Welcome to 'the philosophical poet'&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone, this blog is an outlet for me to share some of the random thoughts and insights I gain whenever they hit me.
Thanks for visiting and feel free to share links to any pieces that you find interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>the_troubled_mind</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/the-troubled-mind.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/the-troubled-mind</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;the troubled mind&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The troubled mind,
like a storm sky,
it rolls tumbles and swirls out of control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The troubled mind,
a mass of pulsating energy,
a trove of limitless possibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The troubled mind,
fuel to my anger,
fuel to my beating heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you felt that kind of limitless rage,
the rage a troubled mind spurns and fuels,
the power and feeling of omnipotence it grows with every ragged breath?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A nuclear bomb in the making,
Boom! Bang! KaBOOM!
It roars and thunders, destroying and transforming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Limitless Power and yet,
here i stand,
alone, and in Ashes...&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>stranger_in_the_mirror</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/stranger-in-the-mirror.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/stranger-in-the-mirror</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;stranger in the mirror&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who are you? What do you want from me?
Do not stare at me so familiarly and do not mock me with your perfect mimicry!
Wait now I understand, oh silly me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How is it possible that I did not recognize you? How can it be that you're a part of me?
I've defined myself by ethics and standards yet proudly you stand as you defy them.
You are me, and I am you, but we are not the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are opposite colors on a yin and yang symbol, how that can be is very simple.
If white be light, and black be darkness, as they have been and will be eternally
You are that little bit of evil, keeping me from being completely pure,
You are that little bit of goodness, keeping me from being completely impure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate you but I need you, you're an elixir but yet still a poison.
You twist and trap me only to set me free.
Disappoint me and then impress me, all with glee&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you will not help me, leave me be!
Do not reinforce bad definitions of me,
And do not do good unnecessarily!
Lest people misunderstand the complex entity that I be&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>mistakes</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/mistakes.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/mistakes</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;mistakes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everybody makes them,
And everybody hates them.
Making a mistake is like rolling dice..
You know exactly what combination or number your going for..
But the probability that you'll get it ...
Is always far less than the probability that you won't.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bummer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulate those around you that seem to be flawless,
Or even just not nearly as flawed as you think you are..
These are either angels,
Or hypocritical actors who have mastered the art of keeping their secrets to themselves,
And on occasion, Lying to themselves so well that even they...
Even they, believe the utter nonsense that they spew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are all alike, plus or minus a few laughs,
A few bad choices, a few unusual circumstances,
A few bad twists of fate, fortune and luck.
Under the right conditions we're all capable of the same things.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>love_trust_and_respect</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/love-trust-and-respect.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/love-trust-and-respect</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;love, trust and respect&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is love? Does anybody truly know?
I could say a million good things about love, I could say a million bad things about it too
But at the end of the day is it bad or is it good? Or maybe just misunderstood?
Does everyone feel the same thing or do we all define it uniquely to suite ourselves?
They say the greatest feeling in the world is to love and be loved, but is it really?
Is not the worst feeling in the world to love and not be loved in return?
What hurts more? To love and not be loved, or to love and not be loved as much?
Why is it we either stay away from the people we love the most or can't stand to be away from them for a single second?
Why does love attract as much as it repels? Why does this one emotion reap as much happiness as sorrow?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is Trust? Is it what keeps us from breaking our promises?
Or is it a tool we use to keep others from breaking theirs?
Is it right to trust someone with your life knowing that they may have to trade theirs to save yours?
Is it wrong to be smart about trusting people because you respect that they may need to break their trust with you in order to keep the trust they have for themselves? Which is more important? Trusting others, or trusting yourself? If we say we trust someone, should we not then be happy with all the choices they make that may or may not affect us?
Should we not have faith that in the long run their decisions are for the better?
Hmmm...do we ever really believe we can trust someone or do we just need to believe it?
Is trust a pretentious belief perpetuated in society that the smarter few may use it to bend other to their will?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is Respect? Should it be earned or given freely?
Should we respect people for what they do?
Or for what they say?
Why respect someone that doesn't respect you?
Why disrespect someone because they don't respect you? We all want respect, but how often do we give it?
Does it not ever seem like the more respect you give, the less you receive?
Has the world not shown us that depending on the situation anything can be respected, good and bad? Does respect not seem more to be measured by achievement than quality of character?
Do you realize some people get more respect from disrespecting than from respecting?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love, Trust and Respect do we give them as much thought as we should? Or do we give them too much thought to begin with?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>hiding_in_plain_sight</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/hiding-in-plain-sight.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/hiding-in-plain-sight</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;hiding in plain sight&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She seeks adventure,
And the wild thrill of new romance..
Her heart is still tender,
But her stubborn spirit's ready to take the chance.
She seeks out her prince, and yet passes me by.
And as I catch a whiff of her sweet fragrance...
I wave...goodbye.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>euphoria</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/euphoria.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/euphoria</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;euphoria&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is this feeling that swells within my chest?
It swells like an inflating balloon, like an over fed tummy
Slow and steady...
A rolling stone gathering no moss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do I suddenly feel like i can fly?
Not so long ago I was being ground to dust by a titanic force
My weeping soul locked behind a wall of pride,
My bleeding heart, desperately beating against a resolute ribcage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But these days it's different...
It feels like I have died and been reborn with a limitless supply of positivity...
It feels like I'm yet to see billions of sunrises...
It feels like everything is gonna work out just fine...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If in the yesterdays of yesterday i was a rock,
Being Eroded and washed away by violent river,
Today I am a fluffy cirrus cloud,
Drifting on a warm, gentle and uplifting breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like some of the best things that happen to us in life.
This recent development bears no explanation.
I could spend forever trying to figure it out...
Or I could do my best to make today last an eternity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pure bliss and satisfaction down one road,
pure chaos and confusion down the other,
The choice isn't a hard one.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>air_or_lead</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/air-or-lead.html"/>
   <updated>2015-06-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/air-or-lead</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;air or lead&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is your love like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it like a gentle uplifting breeze carrying those you hold dear high among the clouds to bask in the warm sunlight?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or is it like a shackle tethering them to the ground...safe, protected and unable to discover the world or themselves fully?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What sort of love would you like to receive? And what kind of love are you prepared to give?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you look beyond your intentions, what lies yonder?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>